http://www.koshervitamins.com/shop/stores_app/security_policy.asp

Ear Care
EFAs (Essential Fatty Acids)
MSM
N-Acetyl Cysteine (NAC)
Beta-Sitosterol
Branched-Chain Amino Acids (BCAA)
Bromelain
Carnitine
Casein
CLA
Coenzyme Q10 (CoQ10)
Catnip
Cayenne (Capsicum)
Echinacea
EFAs (Essential Fatty Acids)
close
.
Ear Care
EFAs (Essential Fatty Acids)
MSM
N-Acetyl Cysteine (NAC)
Beta-Sitosterol
Branched-Chain Amino Acids (BCAA)
Bromelain
Carnitine
Casein
CLA
Coenzyme Q10 (CoQ10)
Catnip
Cayenne (Capsicum)
Echinacea
EFAs (Essential Fatty Acids)
Warning to California Residents
Why does my order include sales tax?
Company Profile
Hours of Operation:
KosherVitamins.com Pledge
KosherVitamins.com is one of the nation's largest Kosher Vitamin retail and mail order suppliers. For over 30 years, we've served Doctors, health professionals and the health conscious community. We offer the best combination of quality services, vast selection, knowledgeable staff, and competitive pricing.
KosherVitamins.com respects our customers' privacy. To better protect your privacy, we provide this Privacy Policy detailing our online information practices and the choices you can make regarding the way your information is collected and used. This Privacy Policy applies to the KosherVitamins.com Web site, www.koshervitamins.com.
KosherVitamins.com will not:
Sell, rent, or lease your personal information
Keep your name on our mailing lists if you've requested to be removed
Share your information with any trading partners unless you've requested information, products, or services that can be best handled by another company
KosherVitamins.com will:
Treat your privacy very seriously and adhere to this Privacy Policy
Promote this Privacy Policy internally so all employees abide by it
Keep this Privacy Policy accurate
Secure Online Ordering System
KosherVitamins.com makes every effort to ensure that your online purchasing experience at is secure. We use state-of-the-art data encryption technology to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your user information. Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encrypts the information sent between your computer and our database, and is certified by GoDaddy, an Internet leader in security transactions. In addition, we use Internet fraud screening to protect credit card transactions.
To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator to tell you that you're viewing a secure Web page. All browsers also display an "s" after the "http" (https://..) in the Web site address to indicate you're in a secure environment.
Credit Card Fraud Warranty
KosherVitamins.com guarantees that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. You pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank generally cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted, through no fault of your own, from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
Protecting Your Credit Card Information.
Hacking database files residing on LAN servers, connected to the Internet, which contain customer data, has been the primary mechanism by which virtually all credit card theft has occurred. Essentially all of the network operating systems whether they were Windows NT, Linux, Unix, or Novell have all been compromised at one time or another.To completely eliminate the risk of a security breach, we have taken the simplest and most reliable approach -- WE DO NOT STORE YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION. This completely eliminates the potential risk of any hacker obtaining valuable data from our systems.
KosherVitamins.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities, and may in its sole discretion disclose personal information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request. KosherVitamins.com reserves the right to release personal information or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Use, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe in our sole discretion that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate the website, or to protect the rights or property of KosherVitamins.com , its affiliates, or any of their officers, directors, or employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. KosherVitamins.com also reserves the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful.
Navigational Information
KosherVitamins.com logs the user's Internet Protocol Address (IP). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your PC every time you browse the Internet. Information from IP addresses is used for system administration to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information — the user session is tracked, but user is anonymous.
Cookies & Data Sharing
A cookie is a small piece of information that Web sites use to remember information about users. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major Web sites use them. Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent or notify you whenever you're sent a cookie. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The cookie itself doesn't tell us who you are, your email address or any other personal information.   To shop online at KosherVitamins.com, your browser will need to be configured to accept cookies.
Koshervitamins.com does not provide any third party with any individually identifiable information other than information necessary to complete your order. Specifically, Koshervitamins.com gives your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. Koshervitamins.com also supplies your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor who bills your account. Koshervitamins.com has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personal information confidential.
If you have additional questions, please email us at info@koshervitamins.com or call our Customer Service Representatives at 1-800-645-1899.
Types of Information Collected
There are two types of information that Koshervitamins.com collects online: (1) personally identifiable information supplied by visitors to our Web site, and (2) non-personal information gathered as visitors navigate through the Web site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity, such as name, address, or email address. KosherVitamins.com collects personally identifiable information from site visitors in the following instances:
When you place an order on our site, we require you to provide your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and credit card information
At the time of ordering, you may also choose to register by creating a user name and password. By registering, you create a user profile which allows us to customize your experience on this Web site, as well as provide a faster method for you to submit a request for information to www.KosherVitamins.com and receive back either the information or products desired
When you voluntarily provide us with your information via a Web form on our Web site, or while corresponding with us via email. It is not necessary to provide any personally identifiable information in order to simply browse our Web site
Non-personal Information
KosherVitamins.com routinely gathers non-personal information, including how many people visit our Web site, the pages they visit, where they come from, how long they stay, their IP address, and the type of browser they used while visiting. None of this information is used to identify you personally.
Non-personal information is gathered through the use of cookies, Web beacons and Web server logs.
A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site sends to a visitor's computer and stored on the visitor's hard drive
A Web beacon is an electronic image, also known as a clear GIF or a single-pixel (1x1). Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on a visitor's computer, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time and date of a page view and a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed. You may render some Web beacons unusable by rejecting their associated cookies
A Web server log is a file where Web site activity is stored. Every time a visitor requests a file or Web page an entry is made into our server logs. These files include the HTML files and their imbedded graphic images and any other associated files that are transmitted to Web site visitors. Log files can be analyzed and summarized by another program
Although KosherVitamins.com uses Web server logs, Web beacons, and cookies on our Web site, we do not know who any visitor is unless that individual specifically tells us.
How We Use Your Information
Personally Identifiable Information
KosherVitamins.com may share your personally identifiable information with trusted third party vendors for the sole purpose of facilitating your order. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. We also may provide your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor that facilitates the transaction. KosherVitamins.com has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personally identifiable information confidential.
Unless otherwise required by law, or if pertinent to a judicial or governmental investigation, or as voluntarily released by you, your personally identifiable information is not shared with other organizations or persons, other than to organizations or persons assisting us in collecting, assembling or processing this information.
In the course of growing or restructuring our business, we may purchase the assets of another company or sell the assets of our company. During these transactions, information about customers is frequently considered a business asset that is the subject of such a purchase or sale. Also, in the unlikely event that KosherVitamins.com, or substantially all of its assets are either acquired or subject to liquidation in bankruptcy, information may be transferred as well. We will require third parties who obtain access to your information as a result of a transaction to adhere to this privacy policy as a condition to transferring the information to them.
Non-personal Information
KosherVitamins.com typically uses the non-personal information we collect in order to better understand how you and other visitors use our Web site, for system administration, to confirm that you've opened the emails that we send you, and to customize your experience when using this Web site. For example, we use cookies to ensure that items added to your shopping cart during one visit are accessible to you on subsequent visits until you either place an order or delete the items from the shopping cart.
Children & Personally Identifiable Information
This Web site is designed for those 15 years of age and older. We will not knowingly collect information of any kind from anyone under the age of 13. If we become aware of a visitor under the age of 13 providing information on our site, we will terminate any accounts associated with that visitor and purge our databases of all information provided by that visitor.
Access, Accuracy and Opt-out Rights
KosherVitamins.com will make every effort to provide you with access to your personally identifiable information so that you may review, update or correct that information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before enabling you to view your data and/or make corrections. If you have submitted personally identifiable information to KosherVitamins.com and would like it removed or modified, please contact us at info@koshervitamins.com. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.
If you don't want KosherVitamins.com to gather non-personal information about you and/or place cookies onto your desktop, you can generally change your cookie and other security settings on your Web browser. For more information, please consult your Web browser documentation. Please keep in mind that if you choose to prevent KosherVitamins.com from placing cookies onto your desktop, you will not be able to shop online at KosherVitamins.com.
If you have registered on this Web site, your personally identifiable information relating to you and your order history are available to you. However, each time you log into your account on this Web site, you will be required to provide the password that you created at the time you registered. After providing your password, you can edit or delete your information at any time through the "Account Info" page.
We will also provide you the opportunity to opt out at any time of certain or all contact from KosherVitamins.com, and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. This choice will generally be offered at the bottom of our online or off-line communications to you. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices, please contact us at info@koshervitamins.com, or:
By Mail: KosherVitamins.com 1215 39th Street Brooklyn, NY 11218
By Phone: Toll Free: 1 (800) 645-1899 Local or international: (718) 686-6112
By Fax: (718) 686-6114
Security
The security of your information is very important to us. Koshervitamins.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive the information. We use state-of-the-art data encryption technology to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your user information. Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encrypt the information sent between your computer and our database. Our ordering system is certified by GoDaddy, an Internet leader in security transactions. In addition, we use Internet fraud screening to protect credit card transactions.
To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator to tell you that you are viewing a secure Web page. Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://..) in the Web site address to indicate that you're in a secure environment.
Third Party Use of Information Collected on KosherVitamins.com
The koshervitamins.com Web site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites.
Koshervitamins.com may share your personally identifiable information with trusted third party vendors for the sole purpose of facilitating your order. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. We also may provide your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor that facilitates the transaction. We also may grant limited access to your name and email address to the agency that deploys emails and other marketing campaigns on our behalf for the purpose of improving our marketing outreach programs. Koshervitamins.com has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personally identifiable information confidential.
Koshervitamins.com may employ additional third parties to provide marketing services on our behalf. With our approval, these third parties may also place cookies onto your computer for analysis purposes. These third party companies will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose. These third party companies will only have access to non-personal information about your visit or transaction, such as the URLS, which lead you to and around our Web site, the pages visited, the product(s) purchased, and the amount spent. These companies will not have access to information that will allow them to personally identify you.
Relationships/Sharing Information:
KosherVitamins.com maintains special relationships with a number of secure business partners. For your security or benefit, when you make a purchase, we may share information about you and the transaction with other companies for many reasons including verification, fraud prevention, credit card authorization, and shipping purposes.
Protection of Children
We never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we actually know are under 15 years, nor is any part of our Web site structured to attract anyone under 15.
Other Important Information
If you have any questions that are not answered by this policy, or you would like more information about any aspect of this policy, please contact us.
KosherVitamins.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications on this Privacy Policy.
Links
Our Web site contains links to other sites with which we associate, or which are outside our service. These other sites may use their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Please be advised, KosherVitamins.com is not responsible for the Privacy Policies and guidelines on these sites. We suggest you review their policies before you utilize their site.
Terms & Conditions
Purchaser, by placing an order, makes an offer to purchase pursuant to these terms and conditions, which offer, if accepted by KosherVitamins.com, is accepted within the State of New York, and purchaser consents to the jurisdiction of the courts of the courts of the State of New York for the limited purpose of dispute arising between the parties resulting from this transaction and agrees that the laws of the State of New York shall apply.
By opening or using a product purchased from Koshervitamins.com, the purchaser agrees to be bound by the term and conditions of sale as set forth below. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of sale, please ship the product back to Koshervitamins.com unopened within 5 days of receipt for a full refund (less shipping and handling charges).
Koshervitamins.com makes no warranty, either expressed or implied, of merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose, and none shall be implied by law.
Please note that the products and the claims made about specific products on or through this site have not been evaluated by KosherVitamins.com or the United States Food and Drug Administration and are not approved to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent disease.
The information provided on this site is for informational purposes only and is not intended as a substitute for advice from your physician or other health care professional or any information contained on or in any product label or packaging.
You should not use the information on this site for diagnosis or treatment of any health problem or for prescription of any medication or other treatment. You should consult with a healthcare professional before starting any diet, exercise or supplementation program, before taking any medication, or if you have or suspect you might have a health problem.
Final determination of suitability of any item sold for the use contemplated by purchaser is the sole responsibility of the purchaser, and Seller shall have no responsibility in connection with such determination.
Koshervitamins.com will not be responsible for any consequential or incidental damages resulting from the sale, non-delivery, use or improper function of any equipment purchased from us. The responsibility, if any is imposed, of Koshervitamins.com in regard to any item purchased shall be limited to the monetary value of the merchandise purchased.
Order Acceptance and Limitations
Order confirmation given to you through Koshervitamins.com does not guarantee our acceptance of your order, nor does it constitute confirmation of an offer to sell. Koshervitamins.com reserves the right to decline and cancel an order, or supply less than quantity ordered at any time.
At times, we may experience a shortage of certain items. At these times, we reserve the right to restrict the quantity of a particular item ordered. We will notify you if a situation like this occurs, In addition . Koshervitamins.com may, at its own discretion, limit quantities sold in each order or to each person or household.
We do not sell to those who intend to resell products offered through Koshervitamins.com, including dealers, resellers, exporters, wholesalers, or customers. Koshervitamins.com reserves the right to decline or cancel an order at any time.
Typographical, Illustration and Price Errors
Koshervitamins.com is intended to be a guide only. Some item illustrations are for display purposes only, may not be exact, and are not necessarily included in the purchase price. Koshervitamins.com is not responsible for typographical or pictorial errors, and specifications may change without notice.
All items offered for sale are subject to availability. Many items on our Web site come from various sources. Koshervitamins.com is, therefore, bound to fluctuating currency exchange rates, making it necessary to occasionally increase prices. In addition, some domestic and overseas products may be discontinued without our prior knowledge. Should this apply to your order, we will, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before shipping or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation.
We make every effort to provide you with an error-free Web site. However, in the event there is a misprint, we reserve the right to correct copy or pricing to reflect the actual current status.
KosherVitamins.com may share account or other information when we are required by law or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection.
You agree that KosherVitamins.com may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information.
KosherVitamins.com also shares information with outside companies that perform services for KosherVitamins.com. For example, when a customer signs up for our e-mail newsletters, KosherVitamins.com will provide the customers e-mail address to third party e-mail distribution companies that transmit e-mails on behalf of KosherVitamins.com. Your e-mail address will not be used by these companies for any purpose other than for the transmission of e-mails for KosherVitamins.com.
We may retain outside companies to assist us in managing our customer information database or to update and correct customer information for future marketing purposes. KosherVitamins.com takes steps to ensure the confidentiality of your information and to make sure it is not used for other purposes.
KosherVitamins.com has carefully selected a few companies to assist us in better understanding how our customers use our site. We will place cookies on your computer to collect information. The information that is collected through these cookies tells us things, such as which search engine referred you, how you navigated around our site, which pages you browsed, what you purchased and what traffic is driven by banner ads and e-mails. The companies analyze the information they collect from our site and return it to us through a secure connection. We use this information to help us understand your interests in our site and how to better serve you. It also helps us provide you with more personalized product offerings.
If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies and still view the site. Because our online ordering system requires cookies, you will not be able to order online, But you can still place an order by phone, fax or mail.
Website Analysis Agent Cookies: We may use a third party to analyze what visitors to our web-site find to be interesting. To do that, they place a cookie on your computer to track the pages you view on our web-site, along with other non-personally Information.
If you have further questions, please feel free to call us Monday - Friday from 10:00 am - 5:30pm Eastern at:
1-800-645-1899 Toll Free (International: 718-686-6112)
Email Exclusives - Sign up to receive amazing deals via email:
Help Center
Contact Us
Track Your Order
Shipping & Delivery
Placing an Order
Return Policy
Payments Methods
International Shipping
Blog
Please note that KosherVitamins.com does not process orders from Friday evening to Saturday evening.
The products and the claims made about specific products on or through this site have not been evaluated by KosherVitamins.com or the United States Food and Drug Administration and are not approved to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent disease. The information provided on this site is for informational purposes only and is not intended as a substitute for advice from your physician or other health care professional or any information contained on or in any product label or packaging. You should not use the information on this site for diagnosis or treatment of any health problem or for prescription of any medication or other treatment. You should consult with a healthcare professional before starting any diet, exercise or supplementation program, before taking any medication, or if you have or suspect you might have a health problem.
© 1999-2020 Kosher Vitamins & Nutrition, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Report a bug on KosherVitamins.com
